OK.
Which customization you're saying David,
this column thing?
Alright.
Yeah, yeah. So look at.
So you see messages and what the six spot.
Yeah.
If I move that to the 4th spot,
it's gonna be showing in every tab in the
4th spot.
OK. Yeah, correct.
So but like that message is meaningless
if I go to the monitoring tabs for
example.
Correct. That'll be blank here,
but it'll be showing up here, right? Yeah.
Right, right.
So this is a question like if you go to
configure your columns on the right.
Yeah.
Yeah, you can do so.
Maybe we can create two profiles,
one for monitoring and one for exceptions
for now.
OK.
Yeah.
Yeah,
one separate profile for monitoring and
one separate profile for this one, right?
Exceptions.
Yeah, well,
I will make sure we have that so everyone
can use it as well as that.
Yeah, OK.
I would want the message to show in the
OK.
column. OK, I think yes, I think so with.
That's customization.
Thank you.
Section.
OK.
OK,
then curious how users will respond to
not having the left to right scroll bar
for the shipment list.
I believe it is already there. It is here.
Is it this the this is the one you're
Oh, OK.
saying?
Yeah, yeah, I couldn't find it.
Maybe 'cause I didn't Scroll down far
Yeah, OK. OK.
enough. OK.
Yeah,
because it requires moving down here and
then going here, right?
Maybe if you just if you're here and then
OK.
doing this, it might not show up.
Because there is 376 records,
you need to come wait to the bottom and
then maybe it might show up, right? Yeah,
so at least.
Yeah.
OK,
I'm I'm logging in just so I can follow
with you guys too.
Because there are two,
like there are two vertical scrolls that
Right.
might be confusing, right?
Yeah.
Or you can add a vertical scroll here so
that if the user can move instead of
going like this and doing it,
you can bring the scroll to the top.
Right.
Or just below or somewhere here so that
they can move it between this these two
models.
Oh I yeah, I see.
Cause I don't use the I I don't use the
the up and down scroll.
I use my mouse for that and that's why I
couldn't find.
Right.
If you if you keep here and then going,
it goes until the record 376,
but if you keep here and do it then you
will get it.
I see. OK.
Yeah, because this activates the inside.
If you keep inside the grid,
this activates this scroll.
But if you keep outside and then scroll,
then it activates this particular scroll.
Yeah, yeah.
I see. OK, OK, yeah,
then that's a curious one.
Let's not change it.
See what the feedback is.
Yeah,
is there a way for users to change column
with? Yeah,
right now this is just as demo.
We don't have it, but obviously yes,
even I was telling Manuela like instead
of adjusting the columns here,
going and adjusting the columns here like
this.
Right.
We should have the option to adjust it
here.
Mhm.
Or adjust the width or width should be
adjusted based on automatically adjust
based on if it is like you know two,
it should put it together right?
It should be shipment and status should
be at the bottom because some of these
spaces is like wasted here also if you
see orders.
Orders can maybe just show one order and
rest.
You can hover and then see the orders,
right? Yeah.
Yeah,
I I don't think I I I would move order
number to the far right.
Like I don't think people care about that.
Yeah.
That really means nothing, right?
That's just a number.
Correct. Yeah. OK.
I don't think users are very interested
But.
in time field on that. Yeah, go ahead.
Yeah,
that's that's why I was asking about it.
So if we can't move the adjust the size,
'cause I think they would just cut off
the time,
then maybe take it out and only show it
on hover.
Because the the feedback is that time is
just a made-up time by the system.
Unless it's an,
unless it's an appointment date field,
the time is kind of ignored.
No, I didn't get your point.
Can you say that one more time?
Did.
The so the date is important,
the time is not.
Oh, time is not OK. OK, yeah.
Yeah, I agree with you.
I I just didn't pay attention to that.
Maybe we can keep this as also hovering
so that you know just you will hover over
this one.
It shows the date and time but just
displays the date here.
Yeah, yeah.
And the only reason I bring that up is
because the real estate's important.
Yeah.
We can.
I can introduce maybe a column width
change like you can select the column to
change the width,
but like I was thinking in doing to all
of them like.
For example,
if you start dragging to the left,
all of the columns will become narrower
instead of just doing one by one.
What do you think about that?
Um.
I mean, it sounds good.
I don't know how well it would work in
Or let.
Oh.
practice. It's hard to say,
you know only cause like when I do that
OK, I have an idea.
in Excel,
like that's the only thing I can compare
it to.
It works for some columns and not others.
OK, yeah, sure. I can.
I can maybe do changes in a stage because
this link is like provided to other
people, right?
And I can show you the stage 1.
Yeah, yeah, you can do it.
And you can say, hey, this is look,
this is fine and we can ship it to the
OK.
big one that this one later or to
validate it right between us.
Bye.
The the other option is like is what John
has just said is if you can somehow make
Mhm.
it wrap tech so we're not wasting the
shipment status space order count, right?
Yeah, that also.
Some of those can be condensed some.
Yeah, true.
Yeah, those can be condensed even.
I think most of the field can be
condensed, right?
So it's like this one that's having all
of it with us.
So similarly we can have one overing
message wherever it goes beyond certain.
Width right?
We can define the width for these and
then wherever it goes beyond that we can
just give an hovering message.
OK. How do you send shipments to overflow?
Yeah, we don't have,
That's a good idea.
don't have those screens yet, right?
It still needs to include those include
as we get the requirements. So this is.
We don't have the screen developed yet
for that,
so we need to select something like the
idea is once this is over.
So then this one,
if you have exhausted all the tender
tender over here and then maybe it will
have an option sent to overflow and then
it creates a new screen and it lists all
the carriers and post it to overflow,
something like that.
That's fine.
I just didn't know if it was Mr.
We haven't gotten there.
Yeah, we don't, we don't have that yet.
So this is just the high level structure
OK.
and how we would want to have it.
But we haven't,
we don't have the edit screen,
ship and edit screen and overflow board,
right.
Those are the ones that we don't have and
maybe the details of within the tender,
right, how?
Tender works and all those things we are
not able to,
but this gives them an idea like how we
would want to show the details. Yeah,
OK.
yeah, send in monitoring.
Can we rename this as Tenderson? Yeah,
what what I thought was not sure if it
breaks any code in net native.
Right,
because this is the current status that
they are using if I change.
No, no, no. So go back to the dashboard.
Yeah, this is the one you're saying,
right? Within this sent, right?
No, no, no, no. Scroll up. Scroll up.
OK.
So right there sent under monitoring.
Uh, OK, OK, this one too. Yes, OK,
that we can.
Yeah, 'cause for for me, it's like what?
What sense, right? We send in that data,
we send to the customer,
we send to the carrier.
Uh, monitoring dashboard. OK, Tencent.
Yes, OK.
Mm.
That we can do.
It makes sense.
The status makes sense because you're
Yeah.
already in the tender page,
so you know they're talking about the
tender, right?
Oh.
Correct. Yeah.
OK, this one, uh,
what I would call this order, right?
Cool.
And you need to use the arrows.
Yeah.
You're in the tender.
Yeah, I should fix that as well.
Yeah, I'm here. Yeah. So this one is here,
right? Order.
So right now we just created something
generic, right?
Yeah.
We don't have what the idea is.
If you click on each of these orders,
order will have its own section, right?
It will have its header section,
then it'll have its.
You know, consigner, consignee,
those will start loading up here, right?
Right.
We are not going to develop a new page
like this.
We are going to pull the information from
the order and then start showing.
So we just kept this information for
general purpose,
but the information would be exactly the
one that they will see in the order.
Right so they will not do except for the
product section.
Product section will come here but
instead of the anything above the product
section right so that will all show up
here that like who it is built to ship
from ship to all this will be as from the
order section. So this is just.
You know,
just a temporary screen right now,
just what we are trying to show,
but all of those will come from order.
That's the idea.
This is so you're basically saying my
feedback has to go to the order team.
Right.
I don't they they're not building it this
way, right.
So you're they are doing section by
section. So they're doing general.
Maybe they have requested they have
multiple accordions, right.
That's how I did see the last design.
So they have multiple accordions.
So all those accordions will show up here.
OK,
but and all I'm asking is to change the
Um.
sequencing and grouping of them.
You don't want that what's white space,
right? Uh, David, that was the.
Well,
I think the what I would do is I'd look
at the white space,
read the comments backwards, right?
So start at the bottom of that section.
Yeah.
Um, so the.
Stay here.
The requested transportation is is not
important, right?
So I don't want that to be one of the
first things they see.
That's number four.
I would switch the total information with
the requested transportation section.
Requested transportation section.
OK total with requested schedule this one.
No, the totals are 22 to the right. Yeah,
right there.
Hi.
Uh-huh. This one.
Yeah,
those totals I would move up to the
second position.
Oh, OK, OK. Oh,
instead of here and this should be OK, OK,
Great.
He.
got it.
Right.
Because by the time we have a shipment,
we're we're not as concerned about what
the requested mode and equipment were,
right. But but the totals,
you know I might be looking at that to
Google.
say is this borderline LTL truckload,
is this the?
You know which order is uh creating the
um multi stop issues because it's too
heavy like things like that.
Mhm.
Um.
And then the next one was just if we
Scroll down like the pickup and delivery
information in order entry has the origin
and the dates together and the
destination and the dates together and
that's all I'm suggesting suggesting is
to in the ship from,
let's have the pickup dates associated
with the ship from.
In the ship to,
let's have the delivery dates associated
to the ship to, which is the next section.
Yeah.
Oh,
you want the delivery dates as well in
here, right? Yeah, got it.
So we can combine some of these, right.
Right. The pick up dates with your, yeah.
Makes sense, yeah.
So this into this. So yeah, correct.
But this is, as I told you,
Yeah.
Because.
this is generally is a general
information, right?
What I was thinking was just to.
Pull this information.
We don't have to develop much,
just pull the information from the order
because order is going to do that.
Right, right.
This is all pulled directly from the
order,
but I but we're responsible for how it's
organized, right?
What I was thinking was we're just going
to leave it as it is, right?
So as per the order,
our order is putting it.
But if you want to put it in a segment
again,
we need to design it in a separate way,
right?
Say for example order keeps it this way,
but we would want to combine this with
Will you?
here and then display means that will be
a separate effort.
That that's fine if if the business has
to see this so that they can get feedback
though.
So I'm assuming they're all doing what I
did and they're critiquing this page.
Correct. Correct. Yeah.
Correct.
OK. Um.
Yeah, but we'll take this input, right?
Once we see the order,
how it is coming up,
then we can see and check with the team
saying can we move some of the
information accordingly and then change
it, right? So that is also a possibility,
but we'll see.
OK.
Yeah,
so that's what I wrote it here saying
that you know all these will be mapped
from order.
This is just an idea for idea of
references.
Then we will bring actual order header
sections here.
OK.
Can we also show OK,
these are all covered.
Can we also show checkbox below the
pickup and delivery date title
appointment? OK, yeah, definitely yes.
So like this right appointment then you
Yep.
would want that date. OK.
And what is the sorry one question,
what is the check box for?
What does it do?
Uh, so it tells you if.
If the date is a pick up,
is it is an appointment?
Basically you check that as yes.
So I I can have an early and a late date
Uh, OK.
right?
That's a pick up between noon and 8:00 PM
or I can check the appointment box and
then that noon becomes the appointment.
That so that that makes it like an action,
right? Like to it,
it actually changes things.
Yeah. So what if, right? Yeah.
And then it would also have to be sent to
Uh.
the carrier.
So the carrier knows instead of pick it
up today, they know, hey,
you have an appointment to pick it up at
Uh.
noon.
OK,
that you know that changes things because
thus this is designed for being just as a
summary. If it does actions,
then we need to I need to realign some of
the languages here.
Oh.
Don't worry that it everything's a hassle,
but.
No, no, no, it's not. It doesn't.
Uh-huh. Tell me.
No, no, it's it's not actions,
it's it's back in logic.
There's there is behind for it.
Yeah, one question I have here David,
like say for example appointment,
OK.
say in case the user would want to add an
appointment,
do you want the user to add appointments
from here which would directly change on
the order or it should be done on the
order so that it can reflect here?
There's different ways.
This appointment is on the order,
so that means it's been communicated to
us from the customer.
OK.
The customer can create an order and say,
hey,
this has to pick up at noon today or noon
Thursday.
Yeah.
All other appointments will be managed
through tracking events.
Or the shipment, right?
Oh, you're you're saying through. OK, OK,
through. OK, got it.
So this is more like a display from the
order, right?
If it has a pickup appointment,
check the appointment and then put the
appointment here.
I believe we have the same under stops if
you see here.
So under stops we have a pick up
appointment somewhere pick up number the
date.
Yeah I think this is the appointment.
So date is this one appointment is 1 CST
right? And then appointment is 1 CST.
Right.
So we have this here.
Right. But yeah,
if you want to include that saying a
check box and saying like, OK,
appointment is there,
then they can also have an idea on it.
Sure. Yeah, we'll do that.
That.
So.
OK product this one I was thinking what I
didn't understand. Was it like floating?
You wanna bring this here and as they
scroll this one remains in the bottom and
then it goes up something like that.
I don't know like I I was just looking
through and I'm like my my first reaction
was like well which field is is the
package ID? Which one?
Cause I and I just got confused and I so
I didn't know.
I think it's because of the lines.
The lines makes it a little bit
Oh, here.
complicated to understand.
See, that looks good.
Oh,
it's because you're saying these two are
Mhm.
together.
So it is like a little confusing saying
whether am I looking at cost or am I
looking at package count,
Yeah, I agree.
something like that, right? Yeah, yeah.
Right.
Yeah,
like the so I I saw the 001 and then the
That's one.
Yeah.
2710 and I was like,
I was curious what the 22710 field was
titled and it took me a second to find it.
That's all.
Oh, OK. Yeah.
OK, this is good.
So I don't know if if you have a
suggestion,
Right.
I just thought it was a little strange.
Right.
I had the same the same feelings in the
beginning. I need to change that.
Yeah, we can either, you know,
mark it in a different way,
put it under a different header, right?
And this is differentiated between this
OK.
and this.
So the focus remains on this particular
box and the user quickly relates this to
this, right, this information.
Mm-hmm. Yeah.
Right. It's just now,
right now it is both are in the same
color, right?
Maybe it is like someone is first time
looking into it.
They might get confused between here and
here.
So maybe we put the focus here when they
Mhm.
click on this particular tab and maybe
grid wise some arrangements are done,
so that should help them.
Quickly figured them out, yeah.
OK, Hazmat would an image better? Yes,
obviously. Where is Hazmat? Yeah,
we have Hazmat as yes,
you want an image next to it.
I was just curious to your thoughts.
Right, definitely.
We can add if it is enhanced, Matt,
maybe an indicator or something. Yeah,
sure. OK, next.
What's the? What's the image for?
Like it's a it's a picture or something.
What do you mean?
Um.
Yeah, picture like a triangle,
warning triangle or something, right?
Uh, to say it's a warning.
It's it's hazmat, right? OK.
Just to say that or some.
Ask Matt. Yeah,
quickly the user will be able to get it
Yeah.
right? So that's it.
OK, don't worry. Um.
OK, no problem.
Mm-hmm.
It.
A box there.
Yeah so this currently they have in TMS.
This is how it has been organized in TMS.
So I did not remove it.
Maybe the idea is maybe we can give hide
it or give one partial view and Click to
expand.
The user will be able to see rest of the
details,
but if they want to see other things
which they got used to right now,
they can still click on this and view.
OK, so you mean you don't need,
you don't need it in the same place,
right David?
Because my my thought was this is context.
Uh, I.
That's why we should keep it before
getting into the table, but I don't know.
I I just think it's redundant.
That's all information that's displayed
Because what would happen David, right?
Say if they are here,
elsewhere.
Huh.
suddenly they would want to see some
appointment or other things, right?
They might have to switch to other tabs.
So the idea is when they are in tender,
right, they get all the information here.
They don't have to jump around other
things, say for example here.
They can see, say for example,
what are all going to get picked up in
one stop, right?
They would have to go to stop and then
see the order, right?
But if they see it here,
it's everything is there in one page and
they would be able to see all the details,
right? The pickup number,
appointment is here, pickup date,
everything is listed. It's it's again.
The summaries that things are getting
repeated, I understand,
but the context is like as Manuela said,
this is a very important screen,
so maybe we just kept the header
information to populate many of those
details.
Which is again, it's there in TMS,
so right if you feel like.
Well,
we're we're replacing TMS for a reason.
So let's let's not compare the the
screens, right?
Sure, yeah.
If you feel that it is redundant,
maybe we can remove it, right?
That is also possible.
Well,
the only reason you need this information
is because it's taking up the space that
has the information right behind it,
right? Which is on the list screen.
I have the delivery,
I have the pickup dates,
I have the equipment, the shipment ID,
right? So if you remove that,
that shipment is displayed on the screen
behind it.
Correct.
Yeah, we can remove it, yeah.
Mhm.
OK,
so this information is the same one as
the in the row, right?
And the the row has the same information.
Yeah.
Yeah, OK, I got, yeah,
maybe we can keep the detail,
the full detail view because it's
scrolling into that row is going to be
more difficult than just clicking.
the button and see, hey,
what is this about?
Well,
I don't think you're gonna be scrolling.
I think a lot of that information is the
stuff that's gonna be moved to the front
of that list screen.
Right, the the pickup,
the delivery locations, the dates,
OK.
the mode, the carrier.
That's what's gonna display as the first
Oh.
The one.
like 9 columns on there.
Yeah, one thing David,
what about we remove this?
OK, uh, that's a good.
Just keep the view full details button
and then keep this alone.
If they want they can see this,
but we can remove this display itself,
right? Keep the button here somewhere.
Mhm.
Yeah.
That work or do you want to just
eliminate that?
OK, because we can save some space,
we can move this button over here and if
That's fine.
the user wants to see some details,
they can click on this one and view it.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, OK, sure, then.
That's a good idea.
And do we need top section? OK, yeah,
this one cost allocation product question.
Will this only populate when a carrier is
accepted?
Should get populated during each carrier
selection process, right? So.
This cost should be a like should be
populated every time, right?
You should have AP as well as an AR cost
every time when a carrier carrier
What? What do you mean every time?
Is that is that tendering or is that
selection happens.
accepting?
This is during tendering.
Rendering if it is sent,
say for example if it is sent right now
OK.
it might be sent and it shows an AP cost.
AP cost is is going to be populated here
and AR cost is going to also come up
because we are calling the we have a cell
shipment at the point of time we are
calling the rating service and getting
this cell shipment the user.
And see the margins for this particular
thing.
Maybe if you want we can say what kind of
status and carrier right to just give
more context that we can do.
Well, no,
because what I'm curious about is would
they need this screen before sending?
They need the screen screen before
sending.
Yeah,
like do do I want to make sure I'm I have
a good barge in before I tender?
Yeah, it it will populate.
So it'll populate before sending based
off of the preferred carrier.
Correct.
Oh,
before sending means you're saying
preferred carrier and this right before
sending it won't populate.
It'll be like after you send maybe
because that is when you call the rating
service, it's not before.
The selection.
Maybe during tendering process it will
call during the evaluation,
OK.
I think so it will get populated during
the evaluation phase, right?
Mhm.
We might have to put that rule saying
that OK during the evaluation process
update this particular screen so that we
can also.
Introduce tender status.
But the question is if they would want to
see that right, let's say here,
can't they see this here?
Directly because you have a AP cost,
I believe we all also we talked about
introducing AR cost here, right?
I did see somewhere we had AR cost.
Where was that?
Yeah, we talk about it. Uh, Jana.
Yeah, we had somewhere AR cost.
Let me see here that will be better to
If you.
keep it here itself, David, right.
So instead of keeping it in the different
page,
we can put AR cost here and if you want
we can introduce margin as well so that
everything is in one page.
If you click the track, Jana, do you?
If you click the track, the track button,
Hey.
A truck.
Oh no, that's not show rate details.
No, no, no, this is edit quote.
Edit quote accepted edition.
Oh,
I think it was in the right details if
Yeah,
that's what I'm trying to see where we
you click it.
If you click the if you click the truck
is a third.
have the cost.
I think it if you click the truck in the
third show rate details.
Yeah.
Ah, here, correct.
Yeah, there you go. That's.
Yeah, here it's.
We have the margin. Yeah, base markup. OK,
as it is. Yeah, markup. Maybe we didn't,
don't have the margin.
We can put the margin and say what is the
margin. Yeah, you left, correct.
So it does an AP cost and then if the
user clicks here show rate details so it
will have all that information.
Maybe I I just I was thinking about
something right now.
Maybe in the column we can we can have a
quick link to that to that page as well
like if you for example click on the AP
cost.
Yeah, maybe we can put it next to, yeah,
some information here so that it can also
Uh huh.
open that information and show right
something we can do that.
Exactly.
Or when you hover it says add view
details and it will it will make you give
you an option to be view details right?
Yeah.
OK.
Is that sounds good?
Or you can.
Yeah, like I have to jump to my next call,
guys.
Yeah. OK.
I think we answered all the questions,
OK.
Alright.
David, as well as the last one, right. So,
OK. Thank you.
Yeah, awesome.
Thank you guys.
Bye.
Thank you guys. See you. Bye, bye.